```xml
<survey>
    <section>
        <title>Demographics</title>
        <question>
            What is your age?
            <answer>20</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Which year of study are you currently in?
            <answer>Second year</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            What is your major or field of study?
            <answer>Sociology with a minor in Environmental Studies</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            What is something you think makes you unique?
            <answer>I have an uncanny ability to connect diverse ideas, often innovating unexpected solutions to social issues, like how to incorporate sustainable practices in activism.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Favorite movie?
            <answer>The Pursuit of Happyness - it embodies resilience, personal struggle, and the pursuit of a better life.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Beer before liquor or liquor before beer?
            <answer>Neither! I prefer to stay mindful and enjoy herbal teas instead.</answer>
        </question>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Problem</title>
        <question>
            What are some of the biggest challenges you face on a daily basis as 
            a college student?
            <answer>Balancing academic responsibilities with my activism, managing social anxiety, and dealing with occasional depressive episodes.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Which of the following issues do you experience the most frequently?
            <answer>Stress</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            On a scale of 1-5, how severe are these challenges for you? (1 - not 
            severe at all, 2 - very severe)
            <answer>4</answer>
        </question>
        <prompt>
            Now imagine someone who you personally think is in a worse situation 
            than you.
        </prompt>
        <question>
            What are some of the biggest challenges that you think they would 
            face on a daily basis as a college student?
            <answer>Increased levels of stress from financial insecurity, lack of academic support, and perhaps significant mental health struggles exacerbated by unhealthy living conditions.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Which of the following issues do you think they would experience the 
            most frequently? (choose one)
            <answer>Financial issues</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            On a scale of 1-5, how severe do you think these challenges are for 
            them? (1 - not severe at all, 2 - very severe)
            <answer>5</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Up or down?
            <answer>Up - always look for the positive!</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Left or right?
            <answer>Left, as I tend to lean toward progressive ideas and social change.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Drake or Kanye?
            <answer>Kanye - I appreciate his creativity and how he pushes boundaries, even with his controversies.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Are you currently using any technology to address the challenges you 
            stated earlier? If yes, please describe.
            <answer>Yes, I use mindfulness apps like Headspace for meditation, and I also leverage online forums to connect with fellow activists who share my drive for social change.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            What features would you like to see in a technological solution for 
            the problems you face?
            <answer>I would love an all-in-one app that not only tracks my assignments and deadlines but also integrates mental health resources, reminders for self-care activities, and a community forum for scholarships and support networks.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            How much would you be willing to pay for a technology solution that 
            effectively addresses your most significant challenges?
            <answer>I would pay around $10 a month, as long as it provides good functionality and resources that genuinely support wellness and organization.</answer>
        </question>
        <question>
            Do you have any additional comments or suggestions regarding 
            technological solutions for college students?
            <answer>I'd love to see an emphasis on social connections within academic environments. A platform that connects students based on common interests or challenges could foster support and inclusivity.</answer>
        </question>
    </section>
</survey>
```