### Demographics

**What is your age?**  
22

**Which year of study are you currently in?**  
Junior

**What is your major or field of study?**  
Environmental Science

**What is something you think makes you unique?**  
I have a knack for turning up at the most unexpected moments to help my friends, whether it’s providing moral support before a big exam or sharing cupcakes during stressful weeks. My ability to lighten the mood keeps our spirits high!

**Favorite movie?**  
*Little Miss Sunshine* - it's a beautiful blend of family dynamics, quirky humor, and the importance of being true to yourself.

**Beer before liquor or liquor before beer?**  
I’d say liquor before beer; I like to start light and save the fun for later!

---

### Problem

**What are some of the biggest challenges you face on a daily basis as a college student?**  
- Balancing academics with extracurricular activities is often tough.
- My tendency towards perfectionism sometimes leads to stress during exams.
- Finding time for self-care amidst a busy schedule can be a real challenge.

**Which of the following issues do you experience the most frequently?**  
Stress

**On a scale of 1-5, how severe are these challenges for you? (1 - not severe at all, 2 - very severe)**  
4 - It's pretty challenging, especially around mid-terms and finals.

**Now imagine someone who you personally think is in a worse situation than you.**

**What are some of the biggest challenges that you think they would face on a daily basis as a college student?**  
- They might struggle with significant financial difficulties while trying to maintain their studies.
- Juggling multiple jobs while attending classes could lead to extreme fatigue and anxiety.
- A lack of support from family or friends may intensify feelings of isolation.

**Which of the following issues do you think they would experience the most frequently? (choose one)**  
Financial issues

**On a scale of 1-5, how severe do you think these challenges are for them? (1 - not severe at all, 2 - very severe)**  
5 - I believe it's a critical and burdensome challenge that can impact their entire academic experience.

---

**Up or down?**  
Up – I always aim for positivity!

**Left or right?**  
Left – I love to be adventurous!

**Drake or Kanye?**  
Kanye – his creativity and willingness to push boundaries in music and fashion inspire me.

**Are you currently using any technology to address the challenges you stated earlier? If yes, please describe.**  
Yes, I use several apps! I rely on Trello for organizing my study schedule and deadlines, alongside Headspace for meditation and managing anxiety. These tools genuinely help me navigate my daily challenges.

**What features would you like to see in a technological solution for the problems you face?**  
- A consolidated dashboard that combines scheduling, mental wellness prompts, and academic resources all in one place.
- Integration of a supportive online community or accountability partners to encourage peer support.
- User-friendly design with customizable reminders for self-care breaks.

**How much would you be willing to pay for a technology solution that effectively addresses your most significant challenges?**  
I would be willing to pay around $10-15 monthly, provided it includes some premium features that enhance my college experience significantly.

**Do you have any additional comments or suggestions regarding technological solutions for college students?**  
I believe a feature that allows students to anonymously share their challenges and seek advice from peers could be beneficial. It could foster community support and encourage open conversations around mental well-being, making college life a bit more manageable and connected.