### Survey Responses 

#### Section 1: Demographics

1. **What is your age?**  
   I am 20 years old.

2. **Which year of study are you currently in?**  
   I am in my second year of college.

3. **What is your major or field of study?**  
   I am majoring in Environmental Studies with a minor in Art.

4. **What is something you think makes you unique?**  
   I have a unique blend of creativity and passion for environmental advocacy; I often express my thoughts about sustainability through my art. 

5. **Favorite movie?**  
   My favorite movie has to be "Into the Wild." It's inspiring and resonates with my love for adventure and nature.

6. **Beer before liquor or liquor before beer?**  
   Honestly, I prefer to keep it simple with just a good drink that’s not too heavy – maybe beer before liquor!

#### Section 2: Problem

1. **What are some of the biggest challenges you face on a daily basis as a college student?**  
   Balancing academic pressure with my desire to engage in extracurricular activities can be difficult. Managing deadlines while ensuring I have time for my social and volunteer work often leaves me feeling overwhelmed. 

2. **Which of the following issues do you experience the most frequently?**  
   Stress

3. **On a scale of 1-5, how severe are these challenges for you?**  
   I would rate this a 4 – quite severe.

4. **Now imagine someone who you personally think is in a worse situation than you.**  
   I think of my friend Sarah, who is a single mother and a college student.

5. **What are some of the biggest challenges that you think they would face on a daily basis as a college student?**  
   She likely faces significant challenges in managing her time between parenting responsibilities and completing her coursework. Additionally, her financial situation adds another layer of difficulty.

6. **Which of the following issues do you think they would experience the most frequently?**  
   Financial issues

7. **On a scale of 1-5, how severe do you think these challenges are for them?**  
   I would rate this a 5 – very severe.

8. **Up or down?**  
   Up! I always prefer to look on the bright side.

9. **Left or right?**  
   Left, as it feels more artistic and unconventional!

10. **Drake or Kanye?**  
    I'd have to go with Kanye – his creativity and ability to challenge norms resonate with me.

11. **Are you currently using any technology to address the challenges you stated earlier? If yes, please describe.**  
    Yes, I use a combination of productivity apps like Notion for project organization and mindfulness apps like Headspace for managing anxiety and stress.

12. **What features would you like to see in a technological solution for the problems you face?**  
    I would love an app that integrates academic scheduling, mindfulness tips, and volunteer opportunities in my area so that I can balance my responsibilities while staying engaged with my passions.

13. **How much would you be willing to pay for a technology solution that effectively addresses your most significant challenges?**  
    I would be willing to pay around $10/month, provided it adds significant value and helps me stay organized and focused.

14. **Do you have any additional comments or suggestions regarding technological solutions for college students?**  
    I think it would be great if apps could collaborate with local resources, providing real-time information on community events and volunteer opportunities, as this would help foster a sense of community and support among students.